wcg.com 2019-07-16

# WCG 2019 Xi’an - World Cyber Games

  * 본문에 이동 en
  * 로컬네비에 이동 en

## PRIVACY POLICY

### WCG Privacy Policy 

About this Privacy Policy

  * We care about your privacy and we think it is important that you always know what information we obtain about you in the context of your use of the WCG websites and participation in our game sports and events and what that information is used for. In the Privacy Policy below, we therefore aim to keep you fully informed as to the type, extent and purpose of the collection, storage, use and processing of personal data arising from your use of or participation in our game sports, events, conferences, festivals (including, among others, WCG 2019 Xi'an, Game Sports and New Horizon) and services relating to these events, including artificial intelligence and virtual reality opportunities and services (the "WCG Events") and any WCG website on which this Privacy Policy is posted (the "Websites"). 
  * Personal data is all information relating to an identified or an identifiable natural person or information that, alone or combined with other information, can identify a natural person, or information that reflects the activities of a natural person. A person is identified when his or her identity can be deduced from the information itself or when we can make a connection to a specific person using additional information available to us.
  * This Privacy Policy applies to the WCG Events and Websites only. You can also see this Privacy Policy at <http://www.wcg.com/about/privacy-policy>. We recommend that you read the privacy policy of every other service provider you make use of, in particular before you make your personal data available to them. 
  * Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. 
  * **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH OUR POLICIES AND PRACTICES, DO NOT REGISTER WITH, OR PARTICIPATE IN OUR EVENTS OR VISIT OUR WEBSITES.**
  * By visiting our websites and using our products and services (including the Events), you acknowledge the terms of this Privacy Policy and the use and disclosure of your personal data as set out in this policy.
  * Our Privacy Policy applies to any user of our websites and participants in our game sports and events.

Who we are

  * We are WCG, Inc., a company located at 5F, Solidspace Bldg. 220, Pangyoyeok-ro, Bundang-gu, Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Korea (" **WCG** ", " **us** ", " **we** " or " **our** "). 
  * We are the organiser of the WCG Events and we host the Websites.
  * We are a provider of game sports, events, conferences and festivals for gaming. 

How to contact us

  * This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and protect your personal data in connection with the WCG Events and the Websites. Respecting and protecting your privacy and your personal data is very important to us.
  * If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personal data, if you need to report a problem, or if you would like to exercise one of your rights under this Privacy Policy you can contact us using the following contact details:: 
    * · Title: Data Protection Officer
    * · Email: privacy@wcg.com 
  * For the purposes of applicable EU data protection legislation, we also have a representative located within the European Union. The contact details of our EU representative are set out below: 
    * · Name: v. KEUSSLER Consulting GbR
    * · Address: v. Keussler Consulting GbR, partnership, Schepp Allee 47, 64295 Darmstadt, Germany
    * · Email: datenschutz@keussler.com 
  * You can contact our dedicated privacy contacts with any queries or complaints regarding your data.

What information we collect

  * We collect certain information about you when you register for or attend our WCG Events.
  * We generally collect information (including personal data) either directly from you (e.g. when you register online for a WCG Event) or indirectly through third party entities that host and/or publish the games for our game sports, and our service providers who help us to organise and produce the WCG Events (e.g. travel agencies). 
  * The information we collect will vary depending on the specific WCG Event you are registered for. However, the range of personal data we are likely to collect for WCG Events is as follows: 
    * · Nickname; In-Game ID; Battlefy Username, Teamname; 
    * · First Name; Last Name; Gender; Nationality; Date of Birth, Place of Birth; Residential address; Marital Status; 
    * · Cell Phone Number; Email; SNS URL; Hash tag; Messenger ID; 
    * · Dietary requirements; T-Shirt Size;
    * · Company name, title and position;
    * · Photo ID; ID Card number;
    * · Passport information; Passport Number (and any previous passport number); Passport Expiration Date, Place of issue; and
    * · Visa application date; Visa application form; Result of Visa application, and any other information required for visa application purposes in accordance with the laws and regulations of the applicable country.
  * During your participation in our WCG Events, we will also collect certain personal data about you. For example, information relating to your participation and progression through the relevant WCG Event. 
  * (When you pay for the WCG Event tickets we receive your payment records (payment amount, name of product, payment date, order number etc.). 
  * If you win a monetary prize at one of the WCG Events, we will also ask you for your bank account and payment details so that we can arrange for your prize money to be transferred to you.
  * We log your visits and use of our Websites using cookie technology.
  * We may collect the following information from you automatically when you visit our Websites: 
    * · Technical information such as the internet protocol (known as IP) address used to connect your computer to the internet, your log-in information, time of access, date of access, time zone setting, web page(s) visited, software crash reports, type and version of browser used, browser plug-in types and versions used, and operating system and platform to ensure the security of your account and to verify that the person operating your account is you;
    * · Your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our websites (including date and time), services you viewed or searched for, page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service team; and
    * · Information about your computer or device allowing us to analyse trends, administer our websites, track your web navigation, and gather broad demographic information for aggregated use. 
  * Depending on the type of personal data in question and the grounds on which we may be processing it, should you decline to provide us with certain data, we may not be able to fulfil our contractual requirements or, in extreme cases, may not be able to continue with our relationship. We will inform you if your failure to provide any requested personal information is going to result in these consequences.
  * **IF YOU DO NOT WANT US TO COLLECT ANY OF THE INFORMATION DESCRIBED IN THIS SECTION, DO NOT USE OUR WEBSITES, OR REGISTER FOR OR PARTICIPATE IN THE WCG EVENTS.**

Linking to third party websites

  * Within the Websites, you may be provided with the option to link through to other websites or services. These other domains, apps and websites are subject to their own privacy practices and we encourage you to read the privacy policies of each and every website and application with which you interact. You visit these other websites or applications at your own risk. 
  * Other websites and applications may use your data differently and have their own privacy policies. You should always read those policies.

Why we collect, process and use your information

  * We collect, process and use your personal data for the following purposes: 
    * **\+ To organise and provide the WCG Events and associated services**
    * · for the purpose of providing and organising WCG Events, including associated services, such as: 
      * broadcasting and production;
      * if you are invited to our events, for travel and logistics, including arranging for your accommodation and meals;
      * if you are participating in our offline events, for visa purposes, including the application and issuance of relevant visas on your behalf;
      * tournament and event administration; and
      * event ticketing;
    * · to post tournament information on our Websites for general users in “participant information” format
    * · to post event photographs/videos via online streaming/broadcasting and on our Websites
    * · for settling fees, facilitating purchase and fee payments, delivery of goods and payment of prizes 
    * · to analyse service use records (for example, Website access information) for analytics and tracking purposes 
    * · for the purposes stated above, we will need to collect and process all the personal data that has been specifically set out in the section "What information we collect"
  * We use your data to organise and provide the WCG Events, the Websites, and any associated services.
  *     * **\+ To manage our participants**
      * for customer services purposes and to deal with any questions, queries or complaints you may have in relation to the WCG Events or the Websites
      * to prevent unlawful and unauthorized use by rogue participants, to check if they want to join, to deal with civil complaints including resolving dissatisfaction and customer advice, to preserve records for any disputes mediation and to give notifications 
      * for the purposes stated above, we will need to collect and process all the personal data that has been specifically set out in the section "What information we collect"
  * We use your data to provide a valuable customer service.
  *     * **\+ Business optimisation and service development**
      * to conduct troubleshooting, research, analysis and product and service development to provide our participants with the best experiences when participating in our WCG Events or using our Websites
      * for the purposes stated above, we will need to collect and process all the personal data that has been specifically set out in the section "What information we collect", except for your dietary requirements and your bank account and payment details.
  *     * **\+ Legal proceedings and requirements**
      * to investigate or address claims or disputes relating to your participation in the WCG Events or as otherwise allowed or required by applicable law
      * for the purposes stated above, we will need to collect and process all the personal data that has been specifically set out in the section "What information we collect
  *     * **\+ For marketing and promotion purposes**
      * for specialization or development of new services (products), to deliver promotional information such as events and to provide services based on demographic information, statistics related to access frequency and the participant’s use of the service
      * for the purposes stated above, we will need to collect and process all the personal data that has been specifically set out in the section "What information we collect", except for your dietary requirements, your bank account and payment details.
  * We use your data to provide you with details of our new products and services.

How long we keep your information for

  * We will not keep your personal data for longer than is necessary for the purposes for which we have collected it, unless we believe that the law or other regulation requires us to keep it (for example, because of a request by a tax authority or in connection with any anticipated litigation) or if we require it to enforce our agreements.
  * Where there is a need to store data because of relevant legislation, for the period stipulated in the legislation, the personal data may be: 
    * · stored for 5 years if records related to contracts or subscription cancellations 
    * · stored for 5 years if records related to supply of goods and payments 
    * · stored for 3 years if records related to customer complaint or dispute resolution 
    * · stored for 6 months if records related to marks or advertisements
    * · stored for 3 months if records related to website visits
  * When it is no longer necessary to retain your personal data, we will delete the personal data that we hold about you from our systems. While we will endeavour to permanently erase your personal data once it reaches the end of its retention period, some of your personal data may still exist within our systems, for example if it is waiting to be overwritten. For our purposes, this data has been put beyond use, meaning that, while it still exists in the electronic ether, our employees will not have any access to it or use it again.
  * We don't keep your data forever.

Your rights

  * You have various rights in relation to the data which we hold about you. To get in touch with us about any of your rights under applicable data protection laws, please use the contact details set out above. We will seek to deal with your request without undue delay, and in any event within any time limits provided for in applicable data protection law (subject to any extensions to which we are lawfully entitled). Please note that we may keep a record of your communications to help us resolve any issues which you raise.
  * In addition, "for users located in the EU only, the European General Data Protection Regulation (the "GDPR") gives you the following rights in relation to your personal data: 
    * **\+ Right to object**
    * This right enables you to object to us processing your personal data where we do so for one of the following reasons: 
      * because it is in our legitimate interests to do so (for further information please see the section on our legal bases for processing below);
      * to enable us to perform a task in the public interest or exercise official authority;
      * to send you direct marketing materials; or
      * for scientific, historical, research, or statistical purposes.
    * **\+ Right to withdraw consent**
    * Where we have obtained your consent to process your personal data for certain activities (for example, for marketing), you may withdraw this consent at any time and we will cease to use your data for that purpose unless we consider that there is an alternative legal basis to justify our continued processing of your data for this purpose, in which case we will inform you of this condition. 
    * **\+ Data Subject Access Requests**
    * You may ask us for a copy of the information we hold about you at any time, and request us to modify, update or delete such information. If we provide you with access to the information we hold about you, we will not charge you for this unless permitted by law. If you request further copies of this information from us, we may charge you a reasonable administrative cost. Where we are legally permitted to do so, we may refuse your request. If we refuse your request we will always tell you the reasons for doing so. 
    * **\+ Right to erasure**
    * You have the right to request that we "erase" your personal data in certain circumstances. Normally, this right exists where: 
      * The data are no longer necessary; 
      * You have withdrawn your consent to us using your data, and there is no other valid reason for us to continue; 
      * The data has been processed unlawfully; 
      * It is necessary for the data to be erased in order for us to comply with our obligations under law; or 
      * You object to the processing and we are unable to demonstrate overriding legitimate grounds for our continued processing. 
    * We would only be entitled to refuse to comply with your request for erasure in limited circumstances and we will always tell you our reason for doing so. When complying with a valid request for the erasure of data we will take all reasonably practicable steps to delete the relevant data. 
    * **\+ Right to restrict processing**
    * You have the right to request that we restrict our processing of your personal data in certain circumstances, for example if you dispute the accuracy of the personal data that we hold about you or you object to our processing of your personal data for our legitimate interests. If we have shared your personal data with third parties, we will notify them about the restricted processing unless this is impossible or involves disproportionate effort. We will, of course, notify you before lifting any restriction on processing your personal data.
    * **\+ Right to rectification**
    * You have the right to request that we rectify any inaccurate or incomplete personal data that we hold about you. If we have shared this personal data with third parties, we will notify them about the rectification unless this is impossible or involves disproportionate effort. You may also request details of the third parties that we have disclosed the inaccurate or incomplete personal data to. Where we think that it is reasonable for us not to comply with your request, we will explain our reasons for this decision.
    * **\+ Right of data portability**
    * If you wish, you have the right to transfer your personal data between service providers. In effect, this means that you are able to transfer the details we hold on you to another third party. To allow you to do so, we will provide you with your data in a commonly used machine-readable format so that you can transfer the data. Alternatively, we may directly transfer the data for you.
    * **\+ Right to complain**
    * You also have the right to complain to your applicable data protection authority. Contact details for data protection authorities in the EU are available at: <http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080>. In addition, for users located in China only, you will have the following rights in relation to your personal data: 
    * **\+ Data Subject Access Requests**
    * You may ask us for a copy of the information, we hold about you at any time, including the personal data, the type or source of such information, the purposes for processing, the identity or type of third parties that have obtained such information. We will provide you with access to the information we hold about you free of charge, we will not charge you for this unless we are permitted by law to charge a fee. If you request further copies of this information from us, we may charge you a reasonable administrative fee. Where we are legally permitted to do so, we may refuse your request. If we refuse your request we will always tell you the reasons for doing so. 
    * **\+ Right to rectification**
    * You have the right to request that we rectify any inaccurate or incomplete personal data that we hold about you. If we have shared this personal data with third parties, we will notify them about the rectification unless this is impossible or involves disproportionate effort. 
    * **\+ Right to erasure**
    * You have the right to request that we "erase" your personal data in certain circumstances. Normally, this right exists where: 
      * We have violated the applicable laws and regulations or our agreement with you in collecting and using your personal data; 
      * We have violated the applicable laws and regulations or our agreement with you in sharing or transferring your personal data with or to third parties, in which case we will notify the third parties to erase your personal data; or
      * We have violated the applicable laws and regulations or our agreement with you in publicly disclosing your personal data, in which case we will cease the public disclosure and notify the recipient to erase the personal data.
    * **\+ Right to withdraw consent**
    * Where we have obtained your consent to process your personal data for certain activities (for example, for marketing), including collecting, sharing, transferring or publicly disclosing your personal information, you may withdraw this consent at any time and we will cease to use your data for that purpose. 
    * **\+ Right of data portability**
    * If you wish, you have the right to transfer to another third party the basic information and identity information we hold on you.
    * To allow you to do so, we will provide you with your data in a commonly used machine-readable format so that you can transfer the data. Alternatively, we may directly transfer the data for you to the extent permitted by then commonly-employed technology.
  * You have a number of rights regarding your data. These rights may vary depending on your location.

Sharing your information

  * In general, your data is processed exclusively by us and we do not pass on any personal user data to third parties unless we need to do so in order to offer you certain WCG Event services. We may share your personal data with the following categories of recipients:
  *     * **\+ Service Providers**
      * In order to provide the WCG Events, we work with service providers (e.g. payment service providers , broadcasters, event organising agency companies and travel agencies) who may, in the course of providing their services, receive and process personal data on our instruction and on the basis of a contractual data processing agreement. 
  *     * **\+ Other participants and/or the general public**
      * We post tournament information on our website for general users in “participant information” format. This information may be viewable by your friends, people at our events, or the public in general. Additionally, photographs and videos taken at the WCG Events may be released to the public by way of online streaming or broadcasting, in addition to being placed on our Websites. 
  *     * **\+ Related entities**
      * We may share your data with certain other entities within the Smilegate group, such as Smilegate Entertainment, Inc. and Smilegate Holdings, Inc. These entities use your personal data for the purposes of providing their own services (including games) to you. Their use of your personal data is subject to their own privacy policies. For further information on how these Smilegate entities process your personal data, please review those privacy policies.
  *     * **\+ Regulatory bodies**
      * We may disclose your personal data to a regulatory authority, government agency or law enforcement body with jurisdiction over our activities.
  *     * **\+ Professional advisors and Auditors**
      * We may disclose your personal data to professional advisors (such as legal advisors and accountants) or auditors for the purpose of providing professional services to us.
  *     * **\+ Replacement providers**
      * In the event that we sell or buy any business assets, we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets. If WCG or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, personal data held by us about our clients will be one of the transferred assets, in which case we will inform you of this condition. 
  *     * **\+ Indicator and tracking analysis tools**
      * We share your personal data with certain entities which provide us with indicator and tracking analysis tools in the Websites. In particular, we use Google Analytics and Tag Manager and therefore share your personal data with Google. For details of how Google uses your data, please visit www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners.
      * Please see the "Cookies" section, below for further information on the cookies which are used as part of the indicator and tracking analysis tools in the Websites.
  *     * **\+ At your option**
      * In certain circumstances, you have the option of sharing information with others yourself as part of the Events (e.g. if you give out personal data in a publically accessible participant or forum profile). However, we do not transfer such data to other third parties.
      * FFor example, within the Events and the Websites, you may be provided with the option to link through to other websites or gaming communities. These other domains, apps and websites are subject to their own privacy practices and we encourage you to read the privacy policies of each and every website and application with which you interact. You visit these other websites or applications at your own risk.
      * You should be aware that personal data that you voluntarily include and transmit online in a publicly accessible blog, chat room, social media platform or otherwise online or that you share in an open forum may be viewed and used by others without any restrictions. We are unable to control such uses of your data and by using such services, you assume the risk that the personal data you provide may be viewed and used by third parties for any number of purposes.
      * Otherwise, your data will only be passed on in special exceptional cases, where we are obligated or entitled to do so by statute or upon binding order from a public authority.
      * You should also note that, as described above, we may receive personal data about you from third parties, particularly any third party that hosts or publishes the game for our game sports.
  * We may share your data with limited third parties (e.g. to help us provide the WCG Events).

Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * We will review this Privacy Policy periodically, and reserve the right to modify and update it at any time. You acknowledge that we may make changes to this Privacy Policy and it is your responsibility to check back to this page from time to time to review the Privacy Policy. Changes to this Privacy Policy will come into effect immediately upon such changes being notified to you or uploaded to our Websites.
  * The terms of this Privacy Policy may change from time to time and you should ensure you know what terms apply to you.

Your California privacy rights and "Do Not Track" 

  * California Civil Code section 1798.83 permits users who are California residents to request certain information identifying any third party to whom WCG may have disclosed, within the past year, personal data pertaining to such user and such user's family for that third party's direct marketing purposes, as well as a description of the personal data disclosed. To request such information, you may contact us using the contact details set out above. Any written inquiry must include "California Privacy Rights Request" in the first line of the description. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per user each year.
  * In addition, California residents under the age of 18 who are registered users of any of online sites, services or applications where this Privacy Policy is posted may under California law request and obtain removal of content or information they have publicly posted. To make such a request, you may contact us using the contact details set out above. Your request should include a detailed description of the specific content or information to be removed. Please be aware that your request does not guarantee complete or comprehensive removal of content or information posted online and that the law may not permit or require removal in certain circumstances.
  * California law permits our users who are California residents to be informed as to how we respond to web browser "Do Not Track" settings. We do not respond to "Do Not Track" settings at this time, whether that signal is received on a computer or on a mobile device.
  * If you are located in California, you have certain additional rights.

Cookies

  * We use cookies (access data files) which save the user's personal information in order to provide a specialized service that is customized and personalized to our users, as well as for analytics and tracking purposes. Cookies are small pieces of data (text files) that are sent by the website server to the user's browser or app and saved on the user's computer and other devices. With respect to its operation, our cookies distinguish between the users' computer or mobile phones but do not differentiate the individual users.
  * You have a right to choose whether the cookies are installed or not. You may choose to refuse all cookies, confirm each time a cookie is saved, or permit all cookies by going to [Tools]>[Internet Option]>[Security]>[Custom Setting], or by using the Settings or Options function on mobile devices. However, if you refuse all cookies, you cannot use our services that use cookies.
  * Our registration site uses Wix software. For further information about cookies and similar technologies used by Wix, please see: <https://www.wix.com/about/privacy>.
  *     * **\+ Google Analytics**
    * The Websites use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (" **Google** "). 
    * Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help us analyse how users use the Websites. These cookies do not collect any personally identifiable information and are only used for the statistical collection of data such as visits and page hits. Google Analytics’ cookies store IP addresses but we cannot link those addresses to any individual or path through the Websites. Google uses the cookies to read information and evaluate visitors’ use of the Websites in the form of statistical reports that we can access. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Websites (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Websites, compiling reports on website activity and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.
    * For further information regarding the way in which Google Analytics uses cookies please see "How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps", (located at www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You can also stop being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites by going to Google's site at: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 
  * We use cookie technology to provide a personalised service to you.

Security

  * We have in place appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect your personal data, including: 
    * · In order to protect the unauthorized disclosure of users' personal data from hacking or any external break-ins, we currently use equipment that blocks any external break-ins, which protects the data from any hacking, attacks, or unauthorized access, and we also use encryption, etc., so that personal data may be transferred safely. In particular, the server containing users' personal data is managed separately so that is not directly linked to the external internet line. 
    * · In preparation for any unexpected emergencies, we have a policy to back-up the system and data.
  * We are taking protective measures to try and minimize damages caused by computer viruses by using vaccines that are regularly updated./li>
  * Only the minimum number of people have right of access to the users' personal data. 
  * We train our staff who handle personal data on new security technology and personal data protection obligations. Further, through an internal designated personal data protection unit, etc., we try and correct any errors immediately upon detection by checking the company's personal data processing procedure implementation and the relevant personnel's compliance with the personal data protection policies.
  * In addition, we have physical security measures in place including limiting access, CCTV installation, setting security levels and limiting physical access based on security levels etc.
  * We take security seriously and put in place measures to protect your data.

Where your information is transferred and stored

  * In general, your data will be stored in the Republic of Korea and China. However, it may be transferred to other jurisdictions. For example, your personal data could be transferred to any country in which a WCG Event is taking place. 
  * In the event that we transfer your personal data to another country and where the country or territory in question does not maintain adequate data protection standards, we will take all reasonable steps to ensure that any such transfers is undertaken in accordance with applicable data protection and privacy laws and that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, please note that where personal data is stored in another country, it may be accessible to law enforcement agencies in accordance with domestic laws.
  * We may store, transfer and use your data outside your country of residence but will always protect your data wherever it is.

Legal bases for processing your information

  * For users located in the EU only, the GDPR requires us to inform you of the different legal bases that we rely on to legitimize our processing of your personal data. We have described these below. 
    * **\+ Where using your data is in our legitimate interests**
    * We are allowed to use your personal data where it is in our interests to do so, and those interests aren't outweighed by any potential prejudice to you.
    * We believe that our use of your personal data is within a number of our legitimate interests, including but not limited to: 
      * To organise, provide and manage the WCG Events and associated services;
      * To manage our users;
      * To provide customer support to our users;
      * For business optimization and service development;
      * To manage our Websites;
      * For marketing and promotion services;
      * To ensure that our systems run smoothly; and
      * To protect against improper use or unauthorized use of our systems and services.
    * We don't think that any of the activities set out in this privacy policy will prejudice you in any way. However, you do have the right to object to us processing your personal data on this basis. We have set out details regarding how you can go about doing this in the section on your rights above.
  *     * **\+ Where you give us your consent to use your personal data**
    * We are allowed to use your personal data where you have specifically consented. In order for your consent to be valid: : 
      * It has to be given freely, without us putting you under any type of pressure; 
      * You have to know what you are consenting to – so we'll make sure we give you enough information;
      * You should only be asked to consent to one thing at a time – we therefore avoid "bundling" consents together so that you don't know exactly what you're agreeing to; and
      * You need to take positive and affirmative action in giving us your consent – for example, we could provide a tick box for you to check so that this requirement is met in a clear and unambiguous fashion. 
    * We currently seek your consent for marketing and advertisement purposes, as well as consent to process your dietary requirements (where applicable). 
    * Before giving your consent you should make sure that you read any accompanying information provided by us so that you understand exactly what you are consenting to.
    * You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time, and details can be found in the "Right to withdraw consent" paragraph in the section on your rights above.
    * **\+ Where using your personal data is necessary for us to carry out our obligations under our contract with you**
    * We are allowed to use your personal data when it is necessary to do so for the performance of a contract that we have with you. For example, if you have won a competition, we need to process your bank account information in order to be able to pay you your prize money. In addition, if we need to apply for a visa on your behalf, we need to process certain personal data in order to do so.
    * **\+ Where processing is necessary for us to carry out our legal obligations.**
    * As well as our obligations to you under any contract, we also have other legal obligations that we need to comply with and we are allowed to use your personal data when we need to in order to comply with those other legal obligations.
  * If you are in the EU, we rely on certain lawful bases to collect, use and share data about you.
  * Effective Date: May 3, 2019
